yellowfx.com 2014-05-19

# Privacy policy - Yellow FX

The following privacy policy is for YELLOW FX users.

The privacy of our users is extremely important to YELLOW FX and the website makes many efforts to ensure the policy is constantly available in many different areas the site to help users gain a solid understanding of how information is used for the purpose of this site.  
Log Files and Cookies

YELLOW FX uses the industry standard analytics packages that automatically gather limited information of visitors to the website. This anonymous information is stored in server log files. The information may include operating system used, basic IP information, IP addresses, referring pages, date/time stamps, and browser type. The information does not identify specific users and it is only used for website administration, trend analysis, and website usage.

Also, cookies may be used to permit easier and quicker access to website features such as logins and multiple visits. Cookies are extremely small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. YELLOW FX links and does not link the information that is stored in cookies to any information type that personally identifies users that have used the site.

The website utilizes persistent and session ID cookies. Persistent cookies may be located on hard drives for long time periods and session ID cookies expire once the browser is closed. Persistent cookies perform many different actions including storing passwords required for forums or blogs so users do not have to sign in every time they visit those areas. Persistent cookies can be used to assist the website in tracking and targeting interests of users to enhance website experience. Session ID cookies allow users to navigate the website in a more effective manner.

YELLOW FX does not have administration or access abilities of any advertiser cookies that are used on the website.  
Links to Other Websites

YELLOW FX displays links to other websites, in which is does not have any control. It is essential for users to understand that if another website link is clicked on; YELLOW FX is not held responsible for that website’s privacy practices or policies. Thus, users are strongly encouraged to read and review the privacy practices and policies of all visited websites.

### Registration and Use of Personal Information

YELLOW FX does not require users to register for access. However, registration may be required for certain features that may be available to users including blogs, forums, and message boards. Registration may be increasingly important for users who wish to submit articles or provide comments on other users’ content in these areas.

If users decide to register and provide the website with information that is personally identifiable throughout the process of registration, they can have complete confidence that any such information will not be shared with any third-party organization without expressed consent.

If is imperative for users to understand that if any articles and comments that are posted to any blog, forum, or message board located on YELLOW FX contain personally identifiable information, the information can be read, obtained and used by all viewers. Hence, YELLOW FX is not responsible for the personally identifiable information that users choose to provide in these sections.

Furthermore, YELLOW FX provides visitors to the website with the opportunity to opt-in to receive website communications. For this purpose, the website asks visitors to provide personal information such as name and email address. The website communications may include newsletters on a regular basis, promotions of products, and any other information that the website feels is important and relevant to its users. Visitors may also choose to opt-out of receiving all or some of the communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided in all emails and replying to any email by typing the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.

Once more, if users provide YELLOW FX with their name and/or email address information to receive website communications, the information will not be shared with any third-party organization unless the user consents to do so.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If users have modifications to personally identifiable information or they no longer want YELLOW FX to have access to this information, users can contact the website to request changes, updates, or removal of the information.  
Security

YELLOW FX abides by the accepted industry standards to make sure any personal information users provide is protected. On the other hand, it is important for users to understand that no electronic storage method ensures 100% security. Therefore, as with any other company, YELLOW FX cannot guarantee that user information will be completely secure.

### California Privacy Rights

The California Civil Code Section 1798.83, often referred to as the “Shine The Light” law, allows users that are California residents to request and obtain information about any personal information that was released to third-party organizations for direct marketing purposes in the prior calendar year. This information can be obtained free of charge one time per year. If this law is applicable, the information that would be included may be a list of categories of shared personal information and all the names and addresses of the third parties. If users are California residents and wish to request information, they can contact us immediately.  
Legal Disclaimer

YELLOW FX reserves the right to release any personally identifiable information that is required by law and when the website believes the disclosure is necessary to guarantee protection of the rights of the website and/or to obey with court orders, legal process, or judicial proceeding that have been served on the website.  
Contact Details

If users have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, they can contact the website using the contact form.
